Ghost Meets Gal!
♬La, la, la♬...
I can't hit the high notes...
These problems take a while if
you solve them the usual way, so...
S-Sleepy...
Alright, Lubna. Can you solve this one?
Miss Petie
Small
Yes! M-M-Me? Uh...
Uhh...
Istilldon'tgetit!
It's an advanced problem,
so it might be a little tricky.
How about Santhi,
who's sitting next to you?
Hmm?
65535, maybe?
Oh, correct!
Santhi's amazing.
Maybe I'm hopeless.
Though I already knew that.
I can't sleep.
Maybe I'll go for a walk.
This might be my first time
coming to the courtyard.
I wonder if I'm really okay like this?
Can someone like me really become an idol?
My, my, a lost little lamb.
I can't say it's proper to be
wandering around at this hour.
Huh?
Welcome to my world.
Looking down, sighing,
hiding my true feelings
Every time i step forward,
even if i'm trembling,
I can't lie to my desire of change!
It's surely a distant dream right now,
but i want to chase it together!
Even if our futures are different colors,
Let's paint them with the same dream.
Because you are the one who gives me courage!